Do you date regular guys? No. I have. Big mistake. You know why? Because I'm not a regular woman.
You know why? Because these ain't no regular times. I date men who consider themselves
extraordinary, who consider themselves capable, who consider themselves responsible
for where things are and where things are going and who are doing things that back it up versus
just talking it up. This is no time for being regular. I know that it seemed revolutionary
to be mediocre at that one point in time, but baby, I simply can't support that because mediocrity
is what has us here in the throes of a white supremacist global imperialism where they're
literally holding on for dear life, white knuckling their way to keep everybody at bay who they
know is better than them. And we're not better simply because we have some sorts of skills
or because we have some sort of talents. We're better because we are more connected to the
universe. We're more connected to the earth because we believe that it matters and we are
of it. I say all that to say that I date men who believe the same because they know that
they have an obligation to not simply be regular, but actually to be spectacular.
See you later.